soundeffectsplus.com 2016-05-16

# SoundEffects+ | Privacy Policy

We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form 

When registering on our site you may be asked to enter your name and e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously but for certain services we require this information. 

We hate spam just as much as you do. We never sell your personal information to third parties. 

Like most websites, we use cookies to enhance your experience, gather general visitor information, and track visits to our website. Please refer to the "Do we use cookies?" section below for information about cookies and how we use them. 

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

• To personalize your experience   
Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs. 

• To improve our website   
We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you. 

• To improve customer service   
Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs. 

• To send periodic emails   
The email address you provide may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your request, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, promotions, related product or service information, etc. Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email. 

• To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature 

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information. These security measures include password protected directories and databases to safeguard your information. 

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use cookies to save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. 

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety. 

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites. 

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent. As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control panel and going to the "My Account" page. 

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not knowingly collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older. 

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline. 

Please also visit our Terms of Use section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website. 

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy. 

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will update the Privacy Policy modification date below. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change. This policy was last modified on 07/07/2015. 

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, feel free to contact us.
